No-No Expedition
Nice Expedition
I am Binzualmu
I'm Waka Yasumori
Ya-hoo!
Pleased to meet you.
Itsu-Men
I see you two are often together.
I'm free.
Is that what this is about?
That's not why they're here.
These two are here today.
They're good bings.
Don't you wish they were more famous?
No, they're serious one-man shows.
So, what are we going to do today?
Let's make an original commercial for e-BEANS!
Let's take e-BEANS to the next level with our own hands!
Yes, completely. Today, the two of us will
We'll be the director of the commercial, and we'll shoot the commercial and show it here.
So, you two know what's good about e-Beans, don't you?
I've had a lot of experiences.
You've been going here for about seven years now.
You've been coming here for about 7 years.
I was here yesterday.
What? Seriously?
Yesterday, in private.
That's how long you've been coming here.
Of course, he knows what makes Eavins so appealing.
So we're going to make a commercial and have you two film it.
So today, we're going to shoot a commercial and you're going to watch it at the end.
You can choose where you want to shoot.
Let's start shooting the commercial!
We've come to goo 10 times, but let's start at the beginning.
I'm Kubokan, and I'm going to shoot a commercial for Fujitani.
Do you have a theme for the commercials that you're going to shoot?
I always aim to make a video that the person I'm showing it to thinks, "This is not good," and then says, "This is not good," and then says, "This is not good," in that 15-second period of time.
I don't know if it's because I'm watching it that it makes me think something's wrong, or if it's because I'm watching it that I feel strange watching it, but it's like it stays in my head.
It's not like it stays in your head or makes you want to go to bed... it's addictive... like it reminds you of something before you go to bed.
It's addictive, like it reminds you of something before you go to bed, and you look at it one more time and wonder what it was all about.
I'm aiming for a drug that is addictive.
I see. So that's why you've come 10 times.
I've been most grateful to you, and I'm sure you've been most grateful to me.
Let's take a picture right here.
First of all, I'm here...
Aah!
Aaah! Beans!
I'll do the "bean" scene.
Just point to it and walk around the first time and you'll be fine.
Ah! Beans!
and say, "Beans!
It's a commercial for EVENS, right?
It's Evens, so it's beans.
All right, action!
Ah! Beans!
Yes, sir.
Yes, okay.
What do you mean?
Oh, beans!
You can cut it once.
What do you mean?
Oh, beans! So, is it OK now?
What?
What do you mean?
What was that?
It's coming, director.
Oh, you saw me, didn't you?
Yes, you did.
That's OK.
Can I cut it off at the "Beans!" part? Can I cut it off at the "beans" part?
Yes, you can.
Once I switch it off.
I'll be able to switch it off, and then the troops will be there and it will start?
Oh, beans! Oh, my God!
You mean don't turn it off until the beans are on?
You don't have to. It's fine either way.
No, I want you to decide, director!
Now it can go either way.
If it's unclear, it's very difficult for us.
I wonder what you're going to do.
It's okay if you don't switch.
Mameuda?
You don't have to cut it once.
Don't do it.
Oh, it's a blister.
If that's the case, I'd like to take another shot.
I got all flustered.
I didn't understand that part.
I'm sorry.
Please do.
All right.
Macho.
Oh, it's a bean!
Yes! Okay!
Thank you very much.
Was it good? The scene you just did.
It was pretty good.
I'm not getting any response from my side.
Are you okay with that?Is everything okay?
Let's start with the standard.
I'll blister here alone.
You say that like you all know me.
But when you say, "I'll blister by myself,
They don't say, "Oh, that's it, isn't it?
This way...
Oh, I got it!
I'm fine.
Are you okay?
Everything's been fine since the last time I saw you.
I'm totally fine.
Even if it's at an angle.
Diagonal?
Can I ask you to try it a little younger?
Diagonal
A slant? A slant like this?
We both go in at an angle.
Yes, I want to make a strange video.
Why don't you start with a straight shot, and then do a slant in the next cut?
I'll show you the first straight shot and then I'll show you the next one.
Then I'll do it.
Why me?
Advice.
Finally, let's all have fun with E-Beans.
It's fun, isn't it?
I know, I know.
You didn't want me to explain.
It's embarrassing.
I thought you might have, but I wanted the fun part.
Please make it fun.
I'd like to take a picture of the E-Beans sign.
Let's move it.
Okay.
I couldn't hear the customer.
I didn't hear the customer.
Thank you very much.
It wasn't a bouquet, it was sunglasses.
For three months, Mr. Yasumori was leading us as the chairman.
Was it that long, this shooting?
Yes, thank you very much.
The weather, you know, there were weather problems.
Yes, it was raining a bit.
Because of the time of the year.
I can only thank Mr. Yasumori for everything he did for us.
Thank you very much.
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished commercial.
I'm thinking of calling for a Season 2.
Please let me play Mame with you!
Thank you very much.
Well then, we're done with Mr. Udari's shoot.
Who's filming Mr. Yasumori's commercial?
Who?
Soo...
Ae.
Kusu.
xoxo
Kukk.
Kuk
Then, let's continue
Uncle Yasun's
Yes, Uncle Yasun
We're filming a commercial...
Yes, sir.
First of all, is this the right place?
Yes, we'd like to shoot here
Yes, yes.
Backstage?
Yes, sir.
This is where we'll take the first shots.
Okay.
Min...
Min is, um... she's a bit of a wimp who doesn't want to go out anywhere.
So you're okay with Mr. Bricitali being his normal self on this couch.
That's right.
Lazy.
You're on your own.
Yes, I'll come running like this.
Come on, let's go.
I say, "Come on," and you force me to wake him up.
I'll catch you like this.
And then I'm like, "Here we go.
And fade out.
And that's the end of the commercial shoot for the two of you.
They've cranked it up.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
It was a great commercial shoot.
They shot two in one day.
We don't have a hard schedule.
We don't have a schedule, so it's hard to shoot two in one day.
Two at once.Put two together.
We shot them.
We finished shooting in about an hour.
That was fast.
I'm going to have everyone who's watching this video
I'm going to show you two videos one at a time.
Do you have any highlights?
Any highlights?
I'd like to say that...
I've been thinking about this project for a year.
That's right.
I asked many times for a proposal.
I've come up with energies and so on.
It took me a long time to come up with this rhythm.
Yes.
I think I was able to make quite a few measures of my life.
It certainly seems to be a turning point, doesn't it, doctor?
Yes, it is.
What about you, Mr. Yasumune?
There was a change of plan for me.
I was taken care of by Genki no Sitting.
I was so sluggish that I couldn't do anything at home.
I went over there and at once.
While I was traveling around Evin.
I was so sluggish that I couldn't do anything at home, but when I went there, I felt better.
That's the kind of theme.
A place that evokes that kind of emotion.
I think that's what I was trying to say.
Yes, it is an inspiration.
There is such a life.
Everyone is crying.
It's really amazing.
It's very common, isn't it, commercials that move you?
"What kind of life do you have, as you are?
Something like, "You and Evins.
What kind of life? It was like an Evins version of that.
It was like an Evins version of that.
It was a commercial that brought tears to the eyes of the viewers.
I was also moved to tears as I was rolling the camera.
When the spot stopped, I could see it.
It's so easy.
I want people to share that with those who are watching.
And I hope everyone will visit Evins.
Yes, that's right.
That's what I'm saying.
We are going to start that commercial now.
Yes, that's right.
Continue in Japan.
Wow! Our gymnastics.
I'd like to show it off, if you'd like.
The video will end here for now.
We will continue with two commercials.
Can I just have the movements?
Please continue with the two commercials for me and Miu Miu!
Oh! Beans!
Bean shavings Bean shavings Bean shavings Bean shavings Bean shavings
Beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans, beans
And
Beans! Beans! Beans!
I'm not going anywhere!
Here, I'm going to the EB room!
Ayu, I'm glad you're feeling better.
Come to the EB room, everyone!